# Mrs. Harshada Sumant Kulkarni

1405, Pragati Skyline, Ragai Mandir Road, Home: 8652726292 Ganesh Nagar, Near HP Petrol Pump, Cell: 9969059857 Dombivli (West) 421202 harshadakulkarni2@gmail.com

#### **OBJECTIVES**

To seek a challenging career in your organization to utilize my knowledge, experience and education to its full potential. Also ready for effectively manages strict deadlines, schedules and repetitive tasks with a positive, can-do attitude.

## **EDUCATION**

- M.Com in Adv. A/c from Mumbai University with 71.15% in 2014.
- B.Com from Mumbai University with 82.29% in 2012.
- H.S.C. from Mumbai Board with 65.33% in 2009.
- S.S.C. from Mumbai Board with 75.38% in 2007.

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Certificate course MS- CIT passed with 80%.
- Certificate course in Advanced Accounting (CAA) which includes Tally ERP 9, MS Word, MS Excel, Advance Excel.

## **SKILLS**

- Knowledge of Internet.
- Worked in Tally, MS Excel, MS Word.
- Bank Reconciliation.
- Maintaining accounting records.
- Preparing accounts and management information.
- Preparing financial statements, including monthly and annual accounts.
- Taxation TDS, VAT, CST, Service Tax.
- Handling bills payable and bills receivables.
- Processing Salary.
- Ledger Scrutiny.
- Handling auditor's queries.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

- ➤ Accounts Executive Valad Business solutions Pvt Ltd. Sept 2015 to April 2017
- Day to Day Accounting;
- Assisting in Finalization of Accounts;
- Handling all the Invoices and petty cash;
- Bank Reconciliation and Account Reconciliation;
- Making foreign payments;
- Preparation of MIS reports. (Weekly and Monthly);
- Attending Audit and Looking after compliances of Audit;
- Salary processing;
- Making online Payment of TDS, PF and ESIC;
- TDS quarterly return.
- ➤ Ass. Management Accounts Radius Global Growth Experts April 15 to Sept 15
- Foreign Accounting.
- > Accounts Assistant Bharat Insulation Corporation (I) Ltd. Sept 2014 to March 2015
- Bank Reconciliation;
- Worked in Tally;
- Invoices Handling.
- Audit Assistant M. P. Chitale & Co. May 2013 to Aug 2014
- Worked in Excel;
- Audit of various Mutual Funds, NAV Verification and Vouching;
- Visited various client places like Citi Bank, Quantum Mutual Fund, etc.

## **PERSONAL INFORMATION**

- Sex: Female
- Date of Birth: 24th December, 1991.
- Marital Status: Married
- Children: 1
- Languages Known: English, Hindi and Marathi
- Nationality: Indian
- Hobbies and Interest: Travelling, Photography, Listening Music.

# **DECLARATION**

I hereby declare that information furnished by me is correct to best of my knowledge and belief.

(Mrs. Harshada S. Kulkarni)